A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller, Vice Presidential records, Press Releases, Series 13 FA382
Rockefeller Archive Center
Nelson A. Rockefeller vice presidential records, Press Releases, Series 13
1973-1977
Rockefeller Archive Center
United States. Office of the Vice President
Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich)
FA382
15 box(es)
Conditions Governing Access note
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Biographical/Historical note
President Gerald R. Ford nominated Nelson A. Rockefeller to fill the vacant vice presidency following the resignation of President Richard M. Nixon in August 1974. Rockefeller served as Vice President from December 19, 1974, to January 20, 1977.
Other Finding Aids note
Detailed finding aids for each series of this collection are available:
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Records, Richard Allison (FA377)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Records, Central Files (FA378)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Records, National Commission on Water Quality (FA379)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Records, New York Office (FA380)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Records, Joseph E. Persico (FA381)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Records, Speeches (FA383)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Records, Working Papers of the Vice President (FA384)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Records, Foreign Affairs and National Security (FA385)
File Plan note
Former Classification: III 26 13
Arrangement
As received.
Scope and Contents
Types of records include: press releases.
Social sciences; Social problems; Social policy; Public policy; Presidential campaigns -- United States; Political science; National security -- United States; International relations -- United States; Public health; Prevention and health; Presidents -- United States -- Election -- 1976; Presidential candidates -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Education; Economics; Economic policy; Drug control; Environmental sciences; Environmental policy; Energy; Education -- United States; International economic relations; Human rights; Government policy; Federal government -- United States; Veterans -- United States; United States; Technology; International relations; Water -- Pollution; Water -- Purification; Vice-Presidents -- United States; Water conservation
- September 23, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents note
  VP Confirmation Hearings, Index to Transcript
- November 21, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- November 22, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- November 13, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- November 15, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- December 11, 1973, 0173-1973 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Albany, New York, Press Release of NAR Resignation as Governor
- August 22, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Newport, Rhode Island, Excerpts of remarks at Jim Nugent Dinner
- August 22, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Washington, DC, State Department News Briefing (Reference to NAR meeting with Henry Kissinger and Foreign Minister Khaddan)
- August 23, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Seal Harbor, Maine, Press Conference #1 re: the role of a VP
- August 23, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Seal Harbor, Maine, Press Conference #2 re: the role of a VP
- August 31, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  White Plains, New York, Press Questions of NAR on arrival at Westchester Airport
- September 3, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  22 W 55th Street, New York City, Press Conference re: Commission on Critical Choices
- September 3, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  22 W 55th Street, New York City, Press Questions following formal news conference
- September 13, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  New York City, New York, Americana Hotel, Excerpts of remarks at Religious Zionists of America Banquet
- September 16, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Washington, DC, Mayflower Hotel, Excerpts of Remarks by NAR at Joint Meeting of Republican National Committee
- September 19, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  Statement by NAR re: net worth
- September 23, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  Statement by NAR before Senate Rules Committee
- September 23, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  Summary of tax returns submitted by Rules Committee
- October 2, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  San Francisco, California, Remarks before 15th Annual Conference of UPI Editors and Publishers
- October 2, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  Provo, Utah, Remarks before student body of Brigham Young University
- October 8, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  Warrenton, Virginia, Press Advisory re: request for additional tax information
- October 8, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  22 W 55th, New York City, Press Questions on departing for Warrenton, Virginia
- October 10, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  Statement by Laurance Rockefeller re: NAR's statement
- October 11, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  Interview with NAR
- October 11, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  Washington, DC, Wire to Congressman Mezvinsky re: release of gifts and loans
- October 11, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  Letter to Chairman Cannon re: gifts to public officials and others
- October 10, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  Statements re: Lasky book and wire to Goldberg
- October 15, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  Remarks by Hugh Morrow re: delay in hearings
- October 15, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  Washington, DC, Press Interview of NAR
- October 16, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  Statement by NAR re: delay in hearings
- October 16, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  Interview of NAR by M. Duenser for Zweites Deutsches Fernsehen (German TV)
- October 16, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  Press Conference of NAR re: Confirmation Hearings
- October 17, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  22 W 55th Street, NYC, Press Conference
- October 18, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  Press Advisory re: release of tax audit and ten year summary of taxes
- October 18, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  Letter to Chairman Cannon re: tax audit and ten year summary of taxes
- October 20, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  NAR response to questions to tax adjustments
- October 20, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  Letter to Chairman Cannon and summary of gifts from 1957-1974
- October 21, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  New York City, Press Questions of NAR on entering hospital
- October 22, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  22 W 55th Street, New York City, Sidewalk interview of NAR
- October 22, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  Statement re: deferring answering questions until after Committee Appearance
- October 23, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  Press Advisory re: attendance at White House Dinner for General and Mrs. Haig
- October 23, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  Press Advisory re: press procedure for departing of Mrs. NAR from hospital
- October 28, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  Letters to Cannon and Rodino transmitting lists of loans from 1952-1974
- November 1, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  Statements by Hugh Morrow re: Jack Nelson's story in NY Post
- November 8, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  Statements by Ralph Blumenthal, NY Times
- November 13, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  Statement before Senate Rules Committee
- November 14, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  Statement by Laurance Rockefeller before Senate Rules Committee
- November 21, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  Page National Airport, Press questions on arrival
- November 21, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  Statement before House Judiciary Committee
- November 24, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  New York City, Press Questions of NAR at Memorial Hospital on Mrs. Nar's Arrival
- November 30, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  Statement amplifying responses to questions of Representative Eilberg on 11/21/74
- December 3, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  Statement by J. Richardson Dilworth before House Judiciary Committee
- December 14, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  Statement by Laurance Rockefeller J. Richardson Dilworth before House Judiciary Committee
- December 10, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  NAR remarks on phone following Senate Confirmations
- December 10, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  Press Questions following Senate Confirmations
- December 12, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  Phone Conversation with Representative McClory and press questions following phone conversation
- December 12, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  22 W 55th Street, New York City, Remarks by Foreign Minister Allen on departure
- December 19, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  Transcript of Inaugural Ceremony as Vice President
- January 10, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  Toast at luncheon for the Sultan of Oman
- January 10, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  Washington, DC, Anderson House, Press Advisory on luncheon with Sultan of Oman
- January 13, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  Statement at start of first meeting of CIA Commission
- January 13, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  Press Briefing following CIA Commission meeting
- January 14, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  Press Release re: Mrs. Rockefeller's tour of Admiral's House
- January 15, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  Statement on the State of the Union Message
- January 16, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  Remarks at President Ford's briefing for Governors and Mayors
- January 16, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  Announcement of Sol Corbin to serve on CIA Commission
- January 17, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  Press Advisory, Congratulations from Mansfield on record
- January 20, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  Press Briefing, CIA Commission
- January 21, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  Washington, DC, Remarks at Outstanding Driver of the Year Award
- January 23, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  Washington, DC, Remarks at Swearing-in Ceremony of the Nuclear Regulatory Committee
- January 23, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  Chicago, Illinois, Press Release re: National Business Leadership Conference
- January 23, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  Chicago, Illinois, Remarks at National Business Leadership Conference
- January 24, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  Swearing-In Ceremony of Marjorie Lynch, Bicentennial Administration
- January 28, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  Remarks at Presentation of the World Wildlife Fund's Getty Prize for Conservation
- January 29, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  Millburn, New Jersey, Remarks at Republican Finance Committee Dinner
- February 3, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  Remarks following CIA Commission Meeting
- February 4, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  Remarks at 2nd Annual USTS State Days Conference (US Tourism)
- February 6, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  Press Briefing of Governor Carey, Mayor Beame and VP
- February 10, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  Remarks after CIA Meeting
- February 13, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  Vice President's announcement of professional staff appointments
- February 13, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  New York City, Waldorf Astoria, Remarks at "Salute to the VP Dinner"
- February 17, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  Remarks following CIA Commission meeting
- February 19, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  Washington, DC, Mayflower Hotel, Remarks at National Governor's Conference
- February 19, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  Washington, DC, US Chamber of Commerce, Hilton Hotel, Remarks at Association National Affairs Conference
- February 24, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  Remarks of David Belin following CIA Commission Meeting
- February 26, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  Detroit, Michigan, Remarks at society of Automotive Engineers
- February 27, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  Remarks at Arthur S. Fleming Awards, Conference Room, EOB
- February 28, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  New York City, New York, St. Moritz Hotel Press Conference on Critical Choices
- March 3, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  Remarks of D. Douglass Dillon following CIA Commission Meeting
- March 4, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  Remarks at National Conference of Christians and Jews (Meany Citation)
- March 7, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  Washington, DC, Hilton Hotel, Remarks at Republican National Committee Leadership Luncheon
- March 10, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 92)
- March 17, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  Remarks of VP and Clark Clifford following CIA Committee Meeting
- March 19, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  Press Release regarding appointment of Thad Garrett
- March 19, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  Press Release of letter to Andrew Stein, Chairman, Temporary State Commission on Living Costs
- March 21, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  Remarks at Coal Conference, East Room, White House
- March 22, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  Washington, DC, Statler-Hilton Hotel, Remarks at Gridiron Dinner
- March 24, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 98)
- March 25, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  Family Theater, White House Remarks at Federal Employees Briefing
- March 27, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 100)
  Press Conference aboard AF II, returning from Saudi Arabia
- March 31, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 101)
  Testimony of William Van Alstyne, CIA Commission
- March 31, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 102)
  Remarks following CIA Commission
- April 2, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 103)
  Washington, DC, Remarks at Transportation Department Meeting re: (Vietnam)
- April 2, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  Vice President's Remarks, Airport, Returning from Niagara Falls Funeral re: (Vietnam)
- April 3, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  Department of Commerce, Remarks at Award Ceremony for Handicapped Federal Employees
- April 3, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 106)
  Remarks at Department of Commerce re: (Vietnam)
- April 7, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 107)
  Remarks at Swearing-In of Henry P. Smith III, Chairman International Joint Commission, U.S. & Canada
- April 7, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 108)
  Remarks Following CIA Commission Meeting
- April 9, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 109)
  Press Conference on arrival at New Orleans (ANPA)
- April 9, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 110)
  New Orleans, Louisiana, Advance text of remarks to American Newspaper Publishers Association
- April 9, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 111)
  Press Conference aboard AF II returning from New Orleans
- April 9, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 112)
  Comments on Stanley Hathaway nomination, Secretary of Interior
- April 9, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 113)
  New Orleans, Louisiana, Q&A following remarks to ANPA
- April 9, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 114)
  New Orleans, Louisiana, Remarks to American Newspaper Publishers Association
- April 9, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 115)
- April 10, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 116)
  Washington, DC, JFK Center, Texts of remarks to President's Commission on Personnel Interchange
- April 11, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 117)
  Washington, DC, Hilton Hotel, Remarks to the National Association of Manufacturers
- April 11, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 118)
  Announcement re: NAR purchase of land in Texas
- April 11, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 119)
  Excerpts of remarks to National Association of Manufacturers
- April 14, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 120)
  Appointment of John Veneman as Counselor to Vice President
- April 14, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 121)
  Press Conference aboard Air Force II en route Taipei
- April 14, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 122)
  Remarks of David Belin, CIA Commission
- April 18, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 123)
  Boca Raton, Florida, Remarks and Q & A to Young Presidents' Organization
- April 20, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 124)
  Statement on Franklin Little
- April 21, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 125)
- April 23, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 126)
  Press Release Excerpts VP Remarks, Advising Council Incorporated Luncheon
- April 23, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 127)
  Press Release Excerpts Vice President's Remarks - Advising Council Incorporated Luncheon
- April 23, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 128)
  Washington, DC, Sheraton Park Hotel, National Academy of Engineering Excerpts of remarks at Marconi Awards
- April 23, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 129)
  Washington, DC, Sheraton Park Hotel, Remarks at Mar3coni Awards, National Academy of Engineering
- April 24, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 130)
  Excerpts of remarks at Library of Congress for 175th Anniversary Bicentennial Opening
- April 24, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 131)
  Washington, DC, Kennedy Center, Excerpts of remarks at National Volunteer Awards Ceremony
- April 24, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 132)
  Washington, DC, National Center for Action, Remarks at National Volunteer Awards
- April 24, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 133)
  New York City, New York, Lincoln Center, Remarks at First Annual Spring Reception, NY Senate Campaign Committee
- April 29, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 134)
  Washington, DC, Washington Hilton, Excerpts and remarks at International General Session of US Chamber of Commerce
- April 29, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 135)
- April 29, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 136)
  Washington, DC, Hilton Hotel, Press Conference following remarks at Chamber of Commerce
- April 29, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 137)
  Washington, DC, Shoreham Hotel, Remarks at Annual Convention of Garden Clubs of America
- April 29, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 138)
  Washington, DC, Shoreham Hotel, Press Conference following remarks at Garden Clubs of America
- May 1, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 139)
  Washington, DC, Sheraton Carlton Hotel, Remarks and excerpts at National Urban Coalition
- May 1, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 140)
- May 1, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 141)
- May 1, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 142)
- May 1, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 143)
  Press Release re: appointment of Governor Raymond P. Shafer as Counselor to Vice President
- May 5, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 144)
  Statement on death of Kenneth Keating
- May 6, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 145)
  Washington, DC, Madison Hotel - VP's Remarks to Institutional Investors Institute - Off-The-Record
- May 9, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 146)
  Hot Springs, Virginia, Press Conference at Business Council
- May 9, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 147)
  Hot Springs, Virginia, Remarks at Business Council
- May 12, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 148)
  Remarks of C. Douglas Dillon following CIA Commission Meeting
- May 16, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 149)
  Washington DC, Mayflower Hotel, Excerpts and remarks at National Republican Heritage Group Council
- May 16, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 150)
- May 16, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 151)
  Press Conference following National Republican Heritage Group Council
- May 16, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 152)
  Washington, DC, Mayflower Hotel, Q&A following National Republican Heritage Group Council
- May 20, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 153)
  Washington, DC, Russell House Office Building, Remarks at Congressional Black Caucus Forum on Employment and excerpts from remarks
- May 20, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 154)
- May 21, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 155)
  Remarks at Award Ceremony Recording for the Blind, EOB
- May 21, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 156)
  House Office Building, Q&A following Bull Elephants Luncheon
- May 21, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 157)
  House Office Building, Remarks at Bull Elephant Luncheon
- June 2, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 158)
  Remarks during CIA Commission Meeting
- June 4, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 159)
  Annapolis, Maryland, Remarks and excerpts at U.S. Naval Academy
- June 4, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 160)
- June 4, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 161)
  Press Release re announcement by VP and Senator Kennedy on White House Science Advisory Conference
- June 5, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 162)
  Press advisory re: allegations of CIA involvement assignations
- June 6, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 163)
  Statement re: White House Science Advisory Conference, New Senate Office building
- June 6, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 164)
  Washington, DC, National Press Building, Remarks to Delta Sigma Chi
- June 10, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 165)
  Washington, DC, Rayburn House Office Building, Remarks before House Science Technology Committee
- June 12, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 166)
  New York City, Waldorf Astoria Hotel, Remarks to New York State Republican Committee
- June 15, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 167)
  Connie Chung interview of VP on Air Force II
- June 24, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 168)
  Announcement re: Ann Whitman's return to New York City
- June 26, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 169)
  Press release re: appointment of Quincy Rodgers
- July 9, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 170)
  Atlanta, Georgia, Remarks and excerpts at National Commission on Water Quality
- July 10, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 171)
  Joint Cabinet Briefing with President Ford and VP
- July 10, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 172)
  East Room, White House, Remarks to Conference of Mayors
- July 14, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 173)
  Washington, DC, Remarks at Awards Ceremony for Colonel Jack Walker
- July 22, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 174)
  Q&A at Midwestern Governor's Conference
- July 22, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 175)
  Cincinnati, Ohio, Netherlands Hilton Hotel, Press Conference
- July 22, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 176)
  Remarks at Cincinnati Midwest Governors Conference
- July 31, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 177)
  Press Release re: appointment of Larry Heath as Counselor to Vice President
- August 5, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 178)
  Washington, DC, Gallaudet College, Excerpts of remarks at World Conference on the Deaf
- August 5, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 179)
  Remarks to White House Summer Interns
- August 6, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 180)
  Austin, Texas, Press Release re: Hospital Productivity Center
- August 11, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 181)
  Press Release re: Admiral's House parties
- August 26, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 182)
  Mobile, Alabama, Press Conference
- August 26, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 183)
  Mobile, Alabama, Remarks at dinner of the Lt. Governors Conference
- August 27, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 184)
  Columbia, South Carolina, Press Conference (2:40 p.m.)
- August 27, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 185)
  Columbia, South Carolina, Remarks at Lace House
- August 27, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 186)
  Columbia, South Carolina, Remarks at GOP Reception
- August 27, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 187)
  Columbia, South Carolina, TV taping with Ed Rowland, Fred McNeese, Jan Stucker
- August 27, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 188)
  Columbia, South Carolina, Press Conference (8:58 p.m.)
- August 29, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 189)
  Warsaw, New York, Attica Grand Jury News Conference
- September 2, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 190)
  Notice to Press re: housewarming events at Admiral's House
- September 5, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 191)
  Rochester, New York, Press Conference
- September 5, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 192)
- September 5, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 193)
  Rochester, New York, Remarks at U.S. Chamber of Commerce Luncheon
- September 5, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 194)
  Rochester, New York, Remarks at NY Chairman's Club Reception
- September 5, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 195)
  Greece, New York, Remarks at Park Ridge Hospital
- September 5, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 196)
  Rochester, New York, Remarks at J. Wholler Farm Center
- September 5, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 197)
- September 12, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 198)
  Morrilton, Arkansas, Remarks at Winrock Farm Reception
- September 12, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 199)
  Dallas, Texas, Remarks at Dallas Republican Women's Convention
- September 12, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 200)
  Dallas, Texas, TV Taping at Communication's Center
- September 12, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 201)
  Dallas, Texas, Press Conference at Sheraton-Dallas
- September 12, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 202)
  Little Rock, Arkansas, Press Conference at Airport Sheraton Motor Inn
- September 12, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 203)
  Little Rock, Arkansas, private residence
- September 12, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 204)
  Little Rock, Arkansas, Remarks at Winrock Farm
- September 12, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 205)
  Oklahoma City, Oklahoma, Remarks at Tinker Air Force Base
- September 12, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 206)
  Norman, Oklahoma, Remarks at residence of J. Blacks
- September 13, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 207)
  Enid, Oklahoma, Remarks at Vance Air Force Base
- September 13, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 208)
  Enid, Oklahoma, Remarks at Oakwood City Club
- September 13, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 209)
  Enid, Oklahoma, Remarks at Republican Committee Dinner
- September 15, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 210)
  London, England, Remarks at U.S. Bicentennial Exhibit
- September 17, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 211)
  Washington, DC, National Archives Reading is Fundamental
- September 18, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 212)
  Washington, DC, State Department, National Academy of Science Lunch
- September 24, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 213)
  Washington, DC, Statement at Presentation of Public Occurrences
- September 29, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 214)